Not man. Not machine. More.
Upgrade is a action, thriller, science fiction film directed by Leigh Whannell.
A brutal mugging leaves Grey Trace paralyzed in the
hospital and his beloved wife dead.
A billionaire inventor soon offers Trace a cure — an artificial
intelligence implant called STEM that will enhance his body.
Now able to walk, Grey finds that he also has superhuman strength and agility —
skills he uses to seek revenge against the thugs who destroyed his life.
Grey Trace, played by Logan Marshall-Green.
Detective Cortez, played by Betty Gabriel.
Eron Keen, played by Harrison Gilbertson.
Asha Trace, played by Melanie Vallejo.
Fisk, played by Benedict Hardie.
Pamela, played by Linda Cropper.
Upgrade is a 2018 cyberpunk action horror film written and directed by Leigh Whannell,
and starring Logan Marshall-Green, Betty Gabriel, and Harrison Gilbertson.
Upgrade follows a technophobe who is implanted with a chip that allows him
to control his body after a mugging left him paralyzed.
The film was produced by Jason Blum, under his Blumhouse Productions banner.
After premiering on 10 March 2018 at South by Southwest, Upgrade was released on 1 June 2018 in
the United States by OTL Releasing and Blumhouse Tilt, and on 14 June in Australia.
The film made $17 million on a $3 million budget and received positive reviews from critics, who called it "one part The Six
Million Dollar Man, one part Death Wish revenge fantasy", and praised its dark humor and action sequences.
The film explores themes of future, artificial
intelligence (a.i.), hacker, police, technology.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.